<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed>
    <chaos>
        <entry>For the rest of the game wear a shoe like a hat. If it drops from your head you drink</entry>
        <entry>Now your name is Bob. Every time someones call you for your real name, he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>You Remember your arabic roots. Every time someone drinks you have to scream like an arabic man, or drink if you forget to do it</entry>
        <entry>You are a lion king fan. Every time you drink raise your glass over your head with both hands or drink again.</entry>
        <entry>Now your name is Betty. Every time someones call you for your real name, he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>Now you are a groupie of Justin Beiber. Every time someone drinks yell "I Love u Justin" with a sissy voice or drink</entry>
        <entry>You were possessed by ghost pirate. Every time someone drinks yell "Aye' caṕtain'" like one or drink if you forget to do it</entry>
        <entry>An Ice witch cursed you. at the end of your turn stay frosty until someone picks the device or drink if you fail.</entry>
        <entry>An evil clown cursed you. You cannot laugh for the rest of the game, drink if u do.</entry>
        <entry>You are Dobby, a slave elf. If you need to re-buy booze, you go. If there was another dobby in the game, he is released and he has to say "Dobby is a free elf" and drink. This cannot be cleansed</entry>
        <entry>You are the Lord of Chaos. Choose someone with a chaos rule and double its drink effect.Make a toast with the victim.</entry>
        <entry>Your life is already too chaotic, pick someone to get the device, and drink one.</entry>
        <entry>Talk to someone like if you were talking to a baby. if she/he laughs, you drink. If both laugh, you drink x2</entry>
        <entry>Now you are a preacher. Yell alleluia every time someone drinks, or you drink.</entry>
        <entry>Now you are the pope. Bless one player with your booze, if he/she curses you, you drink, but if he/she laughs, he/she drink.</entry>
        <entry>Silence Spell!, you cannot talk for the rest of the game. Make someone read for you when is your turn, If you speak from now on, you drink. Important: you read out loud "you drink", drink 1.</entry>
        <entry>Self-Centered Spell! When a player says "Me", "My", or "I", he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>Negate Spell: You cannot say "No" for the rest of the game.</entry>
        <entry>Cursed Mark: The next time the rules are reset, you drink x2</entry>
        <entry>Reflect Mirror Spell: whenever someone makes you drink, that someone drinks too</entry>
        <entry>Voodoo Shaman: you are immune to sacrifice drink effect</entry>
        <entry>Guy Fawkes: you are immune to vendetta drinks</entry>
        <entry>Wild Beast: if there is an animal in the house, whenever it touches someone, that someone drinks. If there are no animals you drink one and yell GreenPeace!</entry>
        <entry>Deja Vu Spell: repeat the last turn played</entry>
        <entry>Greedy: the player with most money in the wallet drinks</entry>
        <entry>Lust: Say something sexual loud or you drink</entry>
        <entry>Gluttony: If someone is eating right now, he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>Wrath: whenever a player curses, he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>Sloth: whenever a player stays 3 turns without drinking, he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>Envy: the player with something red drinks</entry>
        <entry>Pride: the player with more chaos rules drinks</entry>
        <entry>Fluke drink; choose someone, he/she drinks. then he/she chooses another one.</entry>
    </chaos>
</feed>