<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed>
    <chaos>
        <entry>For the rest of the game wear a shoe like a hat. If it drops from your head you drink</entry>
        <entry>Now your name is Bob. Everytime someones call you for your real name, he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>You Remember your arabic roots. Everytime someone drinks you have to scream like an arabic man, or drink if you forget to do it</entry>
        <entry>You are a lion king fan. Everytime you drink raise your glass over your head with both hands or drink again.</entry>
        <entry>Now your name is Betty. Everytime someones call you for your real name, he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>Now you are a groupie of Justin Beiber. Everytime someone drinks yell "I Love u Justin" with a sissy voice or drink</entry>
        <entry>You were possessed by ghost pirate. Everytime someone drinks yell like one or drink if you forget to do it</entry>
        <entry>An Ice witch cursed you. at the end of your turn stay frosty until someone picks the device or drink if you fail.</entry>
        <entry>An evil clown cursed you. You cannot laugh for the rest of the game, drink if u do.</entry>
        <entry>You are Dobby, a slave elf. If you need to rebuy booze, you go. If there was another dobby in the game, he is released and he has to say "Dobby is a free elf" and drink. This cannot be cleansed</entry>
        <entry>You are the Lord of Chaos. Choose someone with a chaos rule and double its drink effect.Make a toast with the victim.</entry>
        <entry>Your life is already too much chaotic, pick someone to get the device, and drink one.</entry>
        <entry>Do like if you are Juggling with imaginary balls, drink if you drop them</entry>
        <entry>Talk to someone like if you were talking to a baby. if she/he laughs, you drink. If both laugh, you drink x2</entry>
        <entry>Make an animal sound. If someone says what animal is, you drink</entry>
        <entry>Yell "THE GAME", everyone that loses drinks. You included, smart boy.</entry>
        <entry>Now you are a preacher. Yell aleluya everytime someone drinks, or you drink.</entry>
        <entry>Now you are the pope. Bless one player with your booze, if he/she curses you, you drink, but if he/she laughs, he/she drink.</entry>
        <entry>Silence Spell!, you cannot talk for the rest of the game. Make someone read for you when is your turn, If you speak from now on, you drink. Important: you said "you drink", drink 1.</entry>
        <entry>Self-Centered Spell! When a player says "Me", "My", or "I", he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>Negate Spell: For the rest of the game negate whatever you say, or drink.</entry>
        <entry>Smurf Spell: if you are the shortest person of this game, everybody else drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Giant Spell: if you are the tallest person of this game, everybody else drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Cursed Mark: if cleanse is played, you drink x2</entry>
        <entry>Better served cold Spell: if vendetta made you drink, the vendetta guy drinks x2</entry>
        <entry>Reflect Mirror Spell: whenever someone makes you drink, that someone drinks too</entry>
        <entry>Voodoo Shaman: you are immune to sacrifice drink effect</entry>
        <entry>Guy Fawkes: you are immune to vendetta drinks</entry>
        <entry>Wild Beast: if there is an animal in the house, whenever it touches someone, that someone drinks. If there are no animals you drink one and yell GreenPeace!</entry>
        <entry>Deja Vu Spell: revive the last turn played when is your turn</entry>
        <entry>Greedy: the player with most jewels drinks</entry>
        <entry>Lust: Say something sexual loud o you drink</entry>
        <entry>Gluttony: the most fat player drink</entry>
        <entry>Wrath: whenever a player curses, he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>Sloth: whenever a player stays 3 turns without drinking, he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>Envy: the player with something red drinks</entry>
        <entry>Pride: the player with more chaos rules drinks</entry>

        <entry>Fluke drink; choose someone, he/she drinks. then he/she chooses another one.</entry>




    </chaos>
</feed>