<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed>
    <chaos>
        <entry>For the rest of the game wear a shoe like a hat. If it drops from your head you drink</entry>
        <entry>Now your name is Bob. Every time someones call you for your real name, that person drinks</entry>
        <entry>You Remember your arabic roots. Every time someone drinks you have to scream like an arabic man, or drink if you forget to do it</entry>
        <entry>You are a lion king fan. Every time you drink raise your glass over your head with both hands or drink again.</entry>
        <entry>Now your name is Betty. Every time someones call you for your real name, he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>Now you are a groupie of Justin Beiber. Every time someone drinks yell "I Love u Justin" with a sissy voice or drink</entry>
        <entry>You were possessed by ghost pirate. Every time someone drinks yell "Aye' captain'" like one or drink if you forget to do it</entry>
        <entry>An evil clown cursed you. You cannot laugh for the rest of the game, drink if u do.</entry>
        <entry>You are Dobby, a slave elf. If anybody needs to re-buy booze, you go. If there was another dobby in the game, he is released and he has to say "Dobby is a free elf" and drink. This cannot be cleansed</entry>
        <entry>Now you are a preacher. Yell alleluia every time someone drinks, or you drink.</entry>
        <entry>Now you are the pope. Bless one player with your booze, if that person curses you, you drink, but if instead he/she laughs, he/she drink.</entry>
        <entry>Whenever a player curses, that person drinks</entry>
        <entry>When a player says "No", he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>When a player says "Me", "My", or "I", he/she drinks</entry>
        <entry>You are cursed. The next time the rules are reset, this curse vanishes from you and you drink x2</entry>
        <entry>Whenever someone makes you drink, that someone drinks too</entry>
        <entry>You are immune to sacrifice drink effect</entry>
        <entry>You are immune to vendetta drinks</entry>
        <entry>If there is an animal in the house, whenever it touches someone, that someone drinks. If there are no animals you drink one and yell GreenPeace!</entry>
        <entry>When someone drinks stay frosty or drink if you fail.</entry>
        <entry>Next time someone has to drink, you drink in his/her place. This rule vanishes when you drink</entry>
        <entry>Next time someone is target of target shot, you take the shot. This rule vanishes when you drink</entry>
        <entry>If someone uses his/her cellphone, he/she drinks. This device user is not considered</entry>
        <entry>Everybody drinks with the left hand</entry>
        <entry>You have to stand up for the rest of the game. If you already are, yo have to sit down</entry>
        <entry>You don't want to drink alone. Everytime you must drink, you choose someone to drink with you</entry>
        <entry>Next Chaos rule. also applies to you</entry>
        <entry>You swap names with the person sitting in fron of you. If someone calls you by your real name. Drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Time to meditate. Close your eyes. If you open them, drink. If you refuse to do it, double the amount when you have to drink.</entry>
        <entry>You are tired. Rest your elbows in any surface. If you lift them, drink.</entry>
        <entry>You are a ghost. No one can talk to you. If they do, they drink.</entry>
        <entry>You are Pinocchio. You can touch your nose, everytime you want, the others must follow you. Last one in touching his nose. Drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Everytime you say "What?" everyone must ask it also. Last one, drinks.</entry>
        <entry>You cannot say "Yes" anylonger, if you do. You drink.</entry>
        <entry>The shortest player, drinks.</entry>
        <entry>The tallest player, drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Everyone with a tattoo drinks</entry>
        <entry>Everyone that is an only child, drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Players who has sisters. drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Players who has brothers. drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Players drinks for each pet they have.</entry>
        <entry>Players drinks for every key in their keychain</entry>
        <entry>Single players drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Player with BF or GF drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Player without driving license, drinks.</entry>
        <entry>Player with piercings drink for each one of them</entry>
        <entry>Players drinks for every ex they had.</entry>
        <entry>Economic crisis. The player with most money in their pockets, drinks.</entry>
    </chaos>
</feed>
